Bill Hering

Information Technology Specialist

- Burlington, New Jersey
- **6** <u>+1 (609) 500-3972</u>
- @ bill@billhering.com
- billhering.com

Profiles

in whering

👔 William H

Skills

Computer Science

 $\neg \neg \neg \neg \neg$

Information Technology

Documentation

Operating Systems

Windows, MacOS, Linux, iOS, Android

Typing Speed 84WPM - 97%

Device Repair Desktop, laptop, tablet, phone, etc.

Software Testing

Networking

Git

Python

C/C++

JavaScript

Java

HTML

CSS

XML

Team Management

problem-solving skills to enhance IT operations. Proficient in maintaining, installing, and troubleshooting hardware and software environments. Highly experienced in supporting end-users. A collaborative team player with a track record of success in customer service, technical support, and operations analysis.

Experienced IT Support Specialist with a strong blend of technical expertise and

Education

Burlington Township High School

September 2016 - June 2020

High School Diploma

Rowan College at Burlington County

August 2020 - Present

Bachelors Degreee

October 2024 - Present

July 2023 - May 2024

Experience

COPA-DATA

Technical Support Engineer 50 Mill Stone Road, Bldg 400, E. Windsor, NJ 08520 https://copadata.com

Framebridge IT Support Technician I

2 Twosome Drive, Moorestown NJ, 08057

https://framebridge.com On-site responsibilities:

- Monitor network issues. Troubleshoot workstation hardware, including Windows PCs, Chrome
- devices, and printers. Collaborate with the software engineering team to resolve issues related to
- our manufacturing system, Joinery, that could not be resolved through IT.
- Monitor security systems, badges, alarms, and cameras. Configure and ship equipment for new store openings.
- Prepare laptops and MacBooks for new employees and have them shipped
- out to remote employees, or staff at our headquarters. Retrieve hardware from ex-employees and prepare them for the next user.
- Remote responsibilities:

Network troubleshooting.

- Software troubleshooting using remote access software such as
- Teamviewer. Troubleshoot retail POS devices such as iPads and card readers.
- Onboard and Offboard users and grant/revoke access to relevant systems.
- Monitor ticketing system and provide support for internal users.
- **Opex Corporation**

Computer Technician https://opex.com

835 Lancer Dr, Moorestown, NJ 08057

May 2021 to July 2023

Take over PC team operations when team lead was unavailable.

machines are non-functional or out of date.

proprietary computer-related components.

• Communicate with Electrical department to ensure sufficient stock of all

- Configure client computer hardware for each customer order and individual need.
- Setup software based on what equipment the computer would be used for. Prepare replacement computers for field technicians.
- Receive obsolete computers and refurbish them as replacements, or scrap if
- Maintain internal network and hardware to ensure peak production efficiency. Configure server hardware for industrial-scale equipment. This includes UPS
- systems, network switches, proprietary power distribution systems, and Windows Server based machines.

IT Support https://crackerbarrel.com

Cracker Barrel

110 Hancock Ln, Mt Holly, NJ 08060

March 2019 - January 2021

Maintain FOH hardware, including POS and Hosting stations.

- Maintain BOH hardware, including security systems, POS hardware, labelmakers, phone lines, and sound systems.
- Ensure all hardware and software constantly up-to-date, and prevent interruptions during operational hours.
- possible, including POS access for staff, and arranging transport for replacement hardware. Provide guests with assistance navigating the Cracker Barrel website to

Collaborate with IT team at headquarters to resolve issues as soon as

References

Joseph Ortega PC Team Lead - Opex Corporation

+1 (856) 577-3137

<u>jortega@opex.com</u>

place or find their order.

Joseph Spiewak IT Manager - Framebridge

+1 (215) 688-0829

<u>joe.spiewak@framebridge.com</u>

Jeremy Rice

IT Support Technician I - Framebridge

- +1 (606) 669-0741
- jeremy.rice@framebridge.com